Michael Chang

Game Developer & Designer Multimedia Artist Based in Los Angeles

Full Stack developer specializing in game with over 8+ years of experience in both designing and developing games. I work mostly with Unity and Blender to create games and applications.

Portfolio: https://mchang0004.github.io/portfolio/

Itch.io: https://mchang0004.itch.io/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-chang-62b89a203/ Email: mchang0004@gmail.com

Education

Loyola Marymount University

B.A. - Multimedia Arts Minor - Computer Science August 2020 - May 2024

The Cambridge Tradition

Creative Writing & Computer Science July 2018 - August 2018

Skills

Coding Languages:

- HTML/CSS/JS

Applications:

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Arduino IDE
- <u>Blender</u>
- OBS/Streamlabs
- Unity
- Unreal Engine

Interests

- Animation and Illustration
- Table Top Games
- Photography Creative Writing



Experiences

Cool Vibes Esports | 2019 - Current | Remote

- Team Manager & Event Coordinator
- · Handles member entry and game competition events

Novalight Games | Jan 2024 - May 2024 | Remote

- · Internship, worked on Unity games
- · QA testing and worked on character/player interaction
- Designing inventory system

EGD Collective | June 2021 - August 2021 | Remote

- Internship and Creative Team
- · At EGD, I taught course on Table Top RPG Design. Multiple presentations on breaking down mechanics and teaching new
- · Also worked on the creative team to create website designs and stream overlays/graphics.

Target | July 2022 - August 2022 | Los Angeles, CA

· General Merchandise Expert

Barn 2 Robotics | 2016 - 2020 | Portola Valley, CA

Component Engineering, Collaboration and Communication skills while working with robotics and CAD modeling.

Projects

KAF | Unity

- · KAF immerses the player in a dream world where they must complete objectives to wake up.
- The game was shown in an exhibition.
- · Available on Itch.io

- Artifacts of Sorellia | Unity
 · Artifacts of Sorellia is a FPS rogue-like card collection game. The game revolves around collecting artifacts to purchase cards.
- · This game was created in 8 weeks for a Unity Development Class
- · Demo available on Itch.io

Stars of Sorellia | Unity

· Stars of Sorellia is an ongoing Unity 2D RPG game. The game is currently in alpha stages. I'm currently working on the developing mechanics and world building. Demo available on Itch.io

Forest Adventure | Javascript

In browse Forest Adventure is a turn-based RPG.